Well, if you're not
going to give me money,
then why are you calling?
She wants to talk to you.
Who's crazy now?
(Leonard:)Hello, Mrs. Latham.
(Leonard:)Yes, I live with him.
(Sheldon:)I don't...
I-I really don't know why.
(Leonard:)Tonight? Sure,
that'd be great.
Okay, I'll see you then.
(Leonard:)Bye.
(Leonard:)She wants to have dinner
and talk about my research.
(Sheldon:)An entire dinner
to talk about your research?
(Sheldon:)Where you going, the drive-thru
at Jack in the Box?
(Leonard:)Well, wherever
we're going,
(Leonard:)she's sending a car
to pick me up.
(Raj:)Okay,
(Sheldon:)- I see what's happening.
- What?
(Sheldon:)My stature intimidates her,
(Sheldon:)so she's using you to get to me.